Utility navigation
------------------

Main navigation
---------------

    * Column one
        * Types of Treatment
        * Who We Serve
    * Column Two
        * Our Approach
        * Additional Services
    * Get Matched to the Exact Support You Need

    * Col 1
        * Conditions We Treat
    * Col 2
        * Treatment Modalities
    * Column One
        * Programs By State
    * Column Two
    * col 1
        * Insurance
    * col 2
        * Admissions
        * What to Expect
    * Get Matched to the Exact Support You Need

    * Col 1
    * col 2
    *       
        
        A Virtual Eating Disorder Treatment Program

    * col 1
        * Support Groups
        * Events
    * col 2
        * Resources
    * 2024 Virtual Eating Recovery and Pathlight Conferences

CTA navigation(ERC)
-------------------

Search 

Suggestions

Common Searches

Menu Menu

Main navigation
---------------

    * Column one
        * Types of Treatment
        * Who We Serve
    * Column Two
        * Our Approach
        * Additional Services
    * Get Matched to the Exact Support You Need

    * Col 1
        * Conditions We Treat
    * Col 2
        * Treatment Modalities
    * Column One
        * Programs By State
    * Column Two
    * col 1
        * Insurance
    * col 2
        * Admissions
        * What to Expect
    * Get Matched to the Exact Support You Need

    * Col 1
    * col 2
    *       
        
        A Virtual Eating Disorder Treatment Program

    * col 1
        * Support Groups
        * Events
    * col 2
        * Resources
    * 2024 Virtual Eating Recovery and Pathlight Conferences

Utility navigation
------------------

CTA navigation(ERC)
-------------------

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information obtained from users of the web site.

The following outlines our privacy policy.

* We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other related purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
* We only will retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of specified.
* We will collect personal information only by lawful means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
* Collected personal data will be restricted to the purposes for which it is to be used as outlined below, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, as accurate, complete, and up-to-date as possible.
* We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
* We will comply with all applicable provisions of the **Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act** of 1996 (HIPAA) as may pertain to information collected from users of our website.
* We will make readily available information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information obtained from users of our web site. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected.

Information Collected
---------------------

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you express an interest in obtaining information about us or our services, when you participate in activities on the Website or otherwise when you contact us.

The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Website, the choices you make and the products and features you use.

Like many businesses, we also automatically collect information through cookies and similar technologies. We may collect the following information:

* directly from you when you voluntarily provide it to us;
* automatically as you navigate through or use our Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, your Internet activity while on our Site and others (e.g., pages viewed, clicks, scrolling and mouse-overs) and other information collected through cookies, web beacons, session replay software and other tracking technologies; and Information about your computer and internet connection, i.e. your IP address, unique device identifier, unique advertising identifier, operating system, and browser type. From third parties, for example, our business partners; and
* From third parties, for example, our business partners.

Purpose of Processing Data
--------------------------

We may use the information we collect from you for the following purposes:

* To provide you with our services and send you information you request.
* To deliver personalized marketing and advertising to you about our services, and to enable additional features on our services and to provide you with a personalized service.
* To provide you with the best service and improve and grow our business, including by understanding our customer base and understanding the effectiveness of our marketing.
* To understand how our services are being used, track site performance, and make improvements.
* To deliver tailored advertising on our Services based on your preferences or interests across services and devices and measuring the effectiveness of ads.
* To protect and secure our services, assets, network, and business operations, to comply with legal requirements, and to detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be fraudulent or illegal.

Data Sharing
------------

We may share data, subject to your consent or other relevant legal basis, with the following third-parties:

* Other companies of our group such as subsidiaries and affiliated companies.
* Trusted business partners providing services on our behalf, such as for technical support, for marketing purposes or for other types of service delivery.
* Governmental authorities and public authorities, as far as this is necessary to provide any services that have been requested or authorized, to protect customers, contractor and partners’ rights, or our or others’ rights, property or safety, to maintain the security of our services or if we are required to do so because of applicable law, court or other governmental regulations, or if such disclosure is otherwise necessary in support of any legal or criminal investigation or legal proceeding.

Depending on applicable law, we implement contracts with some third-parties to ensure that data is processed based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
----------------------------------------------

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Cookies are small files stored by most internet browsers to track visitor information and enable us to make its web-offering more relevant to you.

**What cookies do and why?**

* Strictly necessary cookies: these cookies are necessary for us to provide you with the basics functionalities of our website and cannot be switched off in our systems.
* Performance and analytical cookies: these cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources in order to measure and improve the performance of our website.
* Functional cookies: these cookies are used to provide enhanced functionality and personalization during your visit.
* Targeting or advertising cookies: these cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners to build a profile of your interests and propose you relevant adverts.

Controls for Do-Not-Track Features
----------------------------------

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. At this stage no uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy notice.

European Residents
------------------

If you are located in the European Economic Area, you have certain data protection rights under GDPR. Depending on your interaction with us and your use of our services, we collect and processes your personal information on the following legal bases:

* As necessary to enter into, perform, or terminate a contract with you, and to provide you with, and facilitate your use of, our services.
* Because you have provided consent.
* As necessary to operate our business and pursue our legitimate business interests, where our interests are not overridden by your privacy and data protection rights.
* To comply with the law.

We take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal information.

**Opt-out.** You can contact us any time to opt-out of (a) promotional and marketing communications; (b) any new processing of your personal information that we may carry out beyond the original purpose; or (c) the cross-border transfer of your personal information. Please note that your use of some features of our services may be affected upon opt-out.

**Object.** You can ask us to stop using your personal information where we no longer need it to provide our services or for other legitimate reasons.

**Access.** You can ask us to confirm if we are processing your personal information and you can ask at any time to access the personal information we have collected from you by contacting us directly.

**Update.** You can ask us to correct your personal information if it is wrong.

**Move.** You can request to move your personal information to other companies. You may ask that we provide your personal information in an easily readable format.

**Erase and forget.** In certain situations, you can ask us to stop using your personal information or delete your information, including where we no longer need it to provide our services to you.

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us as set forth below.

In your request, please clearly state (a) what personal information is concerned, and (b) which of the above rights you would like to enforce. For your protection, we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request, usually within a month, and we will tell you if we need additional time.

Please note that, under applicable law, these rights may be qualified, for example, where your information is being used in legal proceedings. We may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete any transactions that you began before requesting the change or deletion, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (for example, for regulatory purposes).

When you receive promotional emails from us, you can also unsubscribe or opt-out by clicking the link provided in the emails. You cannot opt-out of receiving administrative communications (e.g. communications related to your use of our services, or related to your care that we are providing).

California Residents
--------------------

The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) requires us to provide California residents with certain information about how we handle their personal information.

As described in this privacy policy, we collect this information when you visit our websites. We collect information because it is necessary to provide, operate, maintain and support our services, as well as to administer and promote our business. Please refer to the other sections of our privacy policy for further detail.

**Exercising your Rights**

California residents have the right to make the following requests, up to twice every 12 months:

* The right to request the specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.
* The right to request that we disclose what personal information we collect, use, disclose, or sell.
* The right to request that we delete personal information that we have collected about you (subject to certain exceptions).
* The right to opt out of the sale of your personal information.

**You may exercise your rights to access and delete data by contacting us as set forth below.**

This section does not address or apply to our handling of protected health information that is subject to HIPAA or the California Medical Information Act, including any data we collect through your hearing devices or the Thrive app, or to any other personal information subject to an exemption under CCPA Section 1798.145(c) – (f). We do not sell your information for money. We do disclose your information to certain third parties that provide valuable services to us, such as analytics and advertising services, which we do not believe is considered a “sale” under the CCPA. Categories of third parties with whom we have shared personal information in the last 12 months include third-party integrations for advertising and website analytics.

California Civil Code § 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third-parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us and indicate whether you are a California resident.

California law requires us to let you know how we respond to web browser “Do Not Track” signals. Our websites are not currently able to support “Do Not Track” codes. We do not currently respond to or take any action regarding “Do Not Track” requests.

**Non-Discrimination**

We will not penalize you, or discriminate against you, for exercising your rights under CCPA. In accordance with CCPA, should you elect to exercise your rights under CCPA, we will not: (i) deny you goods or services; (ii) charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including by use of discounts, benefits, or penalties; (iii) provide you a different level or quality of goods or services; or (iv) threaten or imply that you may receive a different level of goods or services.

Third-Party Products, Services, and Websites
--------------------------------------------

Please be aware that any third-party websites, software applications, or other products or services linked or accessible via our websites, products, or services are governed by the third-party’s terms of use and privacy policies. You should carefully review a third-party’s terms or use and privacy policies before using the third-party’s products or services.

Children Under the Age of 18
----------------------------

Our Website and services are not intended for children under 18 years of age without the consent of a parent or guardian. If you are under 18 and do not have parental consent, do not use or provide any information on or in our services or on or through any of their features, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal data from a child under 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from a child under 18, please contact us using our contact information below.

Updates to this Notice
----------------------

We may update this privacy notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

Contact Us
----------

You can contact us electronically at [\[email protected\]](https://www.eatingrecoverycenter.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection); by phone at [877-825-8584](tel:877-825-8584) or by U.S. mail or overnight courier at:

**Eating Recovery Center**  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
7351 E. Lowry Blvd, Ste 200  
Denver, CO 80230

4888-5531-1797, v. 1

Eating Recovery Center is accredited through the Joint Commission. This organization seeks to enhance the lives of the persons served in healthcare settings through a consultative accreditation process emphasizing quality, value and optimal outcomes of services.

Organizations that earn the Gold Seal of Approval™ have met or exceeded The Joint Commission’s rigorous performance standards to obtain this distinctive and internationally recognized accreditation. Learn more about this accreditation [here](https://www.eatingrecoverycenter.com/licensing-accreditation "Licensing & Accreditation").

Get Help Now

I am reaching out...

7351 E. Lowry Blvd, Ste 200  
Denver, CO 80230

Call [1-877-825-8584](tel:1-877-825-8584) to schedule a free assessment.

Mon–Fri: 6am–10pm MST  
Saturday: 8am-4pm MST  
Sunday: 8am-4pm MST

[\[email protected\]](https://www.eatingrecoverycenter.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Social (ERC)
------------

Footer (ERC)
------------

* Information For
* Our Centers
* Why ERC
* Resources
* Events
* About

Call to Schedule a Free Assessment

© 2024 Eating Recovery Center. All rights reserved. [Terms & Conditions](https://www.eatingrecoverycenter.com/terms-and-conditions) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.eatingrecoverycenter.com/privacy-policy)
